[Music]
Your body seems to be adapting well to
the changes, Gabriel. This is what you
call well.
Your condition seems relatively stable.
No one's accused me of that in a long
time.
Don't die on me now. You're one of my
finest experiments.
Flattery will get you the grave.
Is there nothing you can do for this
pain? Think of it as fuel beneath the
flames of your vengeance.
[Music]
In the field, doctor, testing a
hypothesis perhaps. With the rate at
which our colleagues get injured, I
expect I'll be testing my patients.
You've been rather quiet today, doctor.
I've gotten a lot done. Can a fish that
never sees the surface know it's
underwater?
There it goes.
If the universe is a simulation, why
aren't there more elephant seals? It
thrills me to put aside my preparations
and humor your brilliant inquiries,
doctor. It thrills me. Kind words. Thank
you.
Have you enjoyed your time away with the
fairies, Dr. Dper? They do make lovely
conversation.
If you know what you're looking for,
inquiry is unnecessary. But if you don't
know, how do you inquire?
Somehow even more tiresome than the
chicken and the egg. Started any wars
lately. I'd have to check my schedule.
You and Hy need to stop frying Sigma's
brain. I'm trying to help your little
friend
and yourself. Yes. So, let's discuss
morality and hypocrisy while we're at
it. You ever broken patient
confidentiality? I can't say. You're
good.
Is carpal tunnel slowing down my WPM? I
can fix it and more. Uh, how about just
taping it up? Offers on the table. What
are you up to, Moira? Wouldn't you like
to know? Fine, I'll hack you later.
You stopping in to see Max? I love how
you make him squirm. It's amusing. I
don't even experiment on Omnics. Yet.
[Music]
Yet.
This foolish mission is taking time away
from my experiments. Aande, think of it
as field work.
I have yet to see a report on your
latest experiment. It's making progress.
Our timeline is non-negotiable. But keep
interrupting me. Surely that'll expedite
things.
How are you feeling, Laqua? I don't
feel. That's the point, isn't it?
You've been distant lately, Laqua. By
your design? Pondering anything unusual?
Dangerous? No, never.
Our foes make such a nuisance of
themselves. Is that an emotion? Did I
detect Laqua?
You are remembering to take your
supplements. Look at these guns and ask
me again.
Moira, I should crush you like a bug for
what you've done. Did you know that
certain centipedes kill prey 15 times
their size? What are you saying? I'm
advising my prey not to test me.
Does it bother you that you've taken as
many lives as you've saved? I don't mind
killing monsters, but go on, keep
pushing me.
How can you experiment on those cute
little rabbits? Easily.
Well, I must never worry about my safety
when the brave agents of Helix are with
us. Don't be so sure about that.
Don't you ever feel remorse for the pain
you have caused. Pain makes one
stronger. You should know that better
than anyone. You have a band-aid. Who
exactly do you think I am? Someone who
carries band-aids.
Guess not.
You look cheery.
As cheery as you are significant.
There is always room for brilliance at
Oasis. I'm honored, but I have some
reservations about your oh, what's the
word? Atrocities, inhumity,
crimes against nature. Huh? Any of those
will do. What is your fascination with
artificial decay? Well, to reverse
entropy, we must tame it. But inflicting
it on yourself? You're withering away.
I've always thrived under a deadline.
So, I'm trying to ask everybody this.
What is your favorite animal?
Scolopendra Gigantia.
Uh, yeah, I can see it. You looking for
a lab assistant? I'm great with
chemicals. Certainly. We would begin by
testing your tolerance for pain. What's
pain have to do with science?
Everything, my strange little friend.
You're the one making abominations.
[Music]
As the strongest woman in the world, you
must see merit in pushing humanity's
limits. All I see is a fool mistaking a
strong body for a gullible mind.
Winston, you were never frustrated at
the restrictions Overwatch placed on
your research. Of course. But sometimes
a measure of caution is needed in a
scientist.
Anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table? Nah.
I know we have our differences, but your
brilliant mind would be welcome amongst
my colleagues in Oasis.
No, thank you. You and your colleagues
discredit the field of science. I want
nothing to do with it.
I'd rather wait a century for progress
than cause the harm you have. What a joy
it must be to feel entitled to patience.
How are you funding your crimes against
humanity these days? My old friend's
innovation and imagination.
A shame you've never met them. How fair
is your research, Dr. Ziegler? Making
much progress through all that red tape?
It's called the hypocratic oath, doctor.
Ring any bells? Aggression is no
substitute for ability. Reckon that's
true. Good thing I have both.
Healing and hurting. H I guess we're not
that different.
I assure you we are nothing alike.
Dr. Leia was not fond of you. Was she
any fonder of you? Of course. I was her
life's work. It seemed to me she was far
more taken with your predecessor.
I must know how your technology
functions. Existence is mysterious,
isn't it?
You have an intense gaze, doctor. I am
thinking on how best to utilize you. In
the coming battle, you mean?
Perhaps.
So, sweet Adena has grown into a
doineering beast. My name is Ortha. You
would be wise to remember it.
Are you breathing petrol or something
more interesting? Want some? No, thank
you. I'll just observe.
Dr. Xiao, I'm interested in your
colleagues research into the long-term
effects of cryogenic freezing.
Oh, well, yes, I am sure. Maybe.
[Music]
I've read your report on cryogenically
preserving severed appendages.
I'd be happy to assist in your research.
No, thank you. I don't think our
methodologies are very aligned. Of
course. I've heard you prefer working
alone.
Look at this world, Symmetra.
See what science has wrought. Of course,
science obeys the laws of nature. It is
only to be expected.
You're a geneticist? If you're up for
it, I bet our bioarchchaeology team
would love to have you. The dead tell
intriguing tales, but my interest lies
with the living. Your state of chronal
uncertainty is fascinating to me,
Tracer. I do wish you'd allow me to
study you. While I'm truly touched by
your offer, I think I'll have to pass.
It seems your little band is back
together for the moment at least.
Overwatch is here to stay. And we're
coming for you next.
Our courageous cowboy.
The years haven't changed you much, have
they, Jesse? No, they certainly haven't
changed my feelings about working with
you.
Hey there, Moira. How have you been?
Busier than you, I'd assume.
Missed you, too. You look great, by the
way. Same saccharine tongue. Same empty
head. I have heard of your experiments.
There is no honor in what you do.
Shimada. Where do I know that name from?
Oh, that's right. The family of
criminals.
I always thought you would understand
better than most the duality of human
existence. I am at peace with it. I
suspect you will be forever unsatisfied.
Much more talkative now, aren't you,
Genji? I find the company more agreeable
these days.
I could have rebuilt you without all
that metal and left me a monster like
other creations. That is a matter of
perspective.
What a nauseating bout of deja vu. Yep.
Working with you has always made me
sick. Are you planning to whine the
whole time again?
I've read about the genetic therapy they
put you through. It sounds unpleasant.
It was, but ignorance was worse. Don't
bother. Reason is lost on her.
I cannot believe I am being subjected to
this cacophony.
And they say my actions are unethical.
No, I am not enjoying this.
Timicowsa
Estes
Senica said that the cause of fear is
ignorance. If only anyone had listened.
They say a banshee haunts these grounds,
but those are just fairy tales.
A dreamer is one who can only find his
way by moonlight. And his punishment is
that he sees the dawn before the rest of
the world.
We are all in the gutter, but some of us
are looking at the stars.
Yet another stretch of cloudless skies
and idyllic ocean views.
Wonderful.
I tend to avoid places this crowded
h beings born of science seeking answers
in faith.
Nenton
fame.
This city brings back memories.
Overwatch.
Keepers of the status quo.
Swift as the wind and dim as the night.
A procedure gone arry. There is but one
cure for madness.
Such misplaced optimism.
You should have kept running. The milk
of human kindness has spoiled. All
experiments must come to an end. What
have you become? Tor sha. Do not meddle
in my affairs.
Be the histabra.
A life best left forgotten.
This specimen has been disposed of. This
power is intriguing, Amari.
Even heroes are cursed with mortality.
At least your body is well preserved.
Back in your cage, doctor.
Must I do your work as well as my own,
Gabriel?
Are your thorns just for show?
Must you be coddled, Proximony?
Seems I've made a habit of saving your
life, Gabriel.
Try using your head along with your
fists.
A rose clipped too soon. Can't charm
your way out of this one. It is often
one's mouth breaks her nose. A revoir
masher.
A stinging nettle.
I see why biolyte is so desirable.
You're rather heartless for a man with
two of them.
Mind your hypocrisy, doctor. Truly
inspiring work, doctor. About time you
were of use.
I respect those who hold to their
values.
Haridan, mercy is for the weak. Your
involvement in my research is at an end.
[Music]